



CONTACT

- milliance23@gmail.com
- Street São Lourenço, 210, house 21, Niterói - RJ
- + 55 21972141165
- Haitian

LANGUAGES

- Native Creole
- Intermediary English
- Native French
- Advanced Portuguese

SKILLS

- MongoDB
- Python
- MySQL
- Java
- AngularJS
- React.JS
- lavaScript

LINKEDIN

https://www.linkedin.com/in/ handy-claude-marie-milliance-95785099/

GITHUB

• https://github.com/han19githtbr

PORTFOLIO

• https://portfolio-handy.netlify.app/

HANDY CLAUDE MARIE MILLIANCE

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

GOAL

I'm looking for a Full Stack development position. I am willing to learn, and I am ready to face new challenges

SUMMARY

I graduated from the Bachelor's degree in Computer Science at the Federal Rural University of Rio de Janeiro, in June 2022. Almost at the end of my degree, I interned in Web Development for 1 year and 4 months at the Attorney General's Office of the Municipality of Nova Iguaçu. To improve myself as a Full Stack Developer, I took other courses where I learned how to develop complete applications using mainly technologies such as: Java, Angular, React.JS, MySQL and MongoDB.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

Meraki Smart Systems. Remote | 05/2023 - 05/2023

Development and Maintenance of Software and Applications. Technologies and languages used: Angular, C#

FULL STACK RESEARCHER AND DEVELOPER

Connaissance en Action, study group Rio de Janeiro - RJ | 01/2021 - 09/2023

Connaissance en Action is a multidisciplinary study group that aims to develop complete projects and applications using modern market technologies. Technologies and languages used in the project: Angular, Java, Typescript, Spring Boot, MySQL, Git, GitHub.

FREELANCE DEVELOPER

NODRIC STUDIO. Cabo Frio - RJ | 11/2022 - 12/2022

Development of a website on the WIX platform, for an Architecture company. Technologies and languages used: Html, Css and Javascript.

WEB DEVELOPMENT INTERN

Attorney General's Office of the Municipality of Nova Iguaçu. Nova Iguaçu - RJ | 04/12/2021 - 07/31/2022

1 Assistance in the development of systems for the needs of the Prosecutor's Office, as well as support and

maintenance of systems. 2 Assistance in the development of the Institutional Website. 3 Provision of support to Public Prosecutor's Office employees, aiming to find technological solutions to solve the various problems that arise in daily work. 4 Support for the databases on which the Prosecutor's Office systems are

based, developed by the IT team. Technologies used: Wordpress, Html, Css, Javascript, Java, Spring Boot.

EDUCATION

BOOTCAMP SANTANDER FULL STACK JAVA + ANGULAR

Santander Universities. Online | 08/16/2023 - 10/22/2023

FULL STACK DEVELOPMENT COURSE

TOTI. Rio de Janeiro - RJ | 04/2022 - 08/2022

BACHELOR OF COMPUTER SCIENCE

Federal Rural University of Rio de Janeiro. Nova Iguaçu - RJ | 04/2014 - 06/2022